Guide to the People for the Ethical Treatment of Animals (PETA) Research Files
People for the Ethical Treatment of Animals (PETA) Research Files
- Confidential Subject Files, 11.5 linear feet
  - Turtles—Correspondence - General (Box 131, Folder 8)
  - Turtles—Correspondence with PETA Europe (Box 131, Folder 9)
  - Turtles—Ichinose’s Manuscript and Publication (against the use of live turtles in physiology courses for colleges; correspondence.) (Box 131, Folder 10)
  - Turtles—Literature—Education (Box 131, Folder 11)
  - Turtles—Literature—Food and pets (Box 131, Folder 12)
  - Turtles—Literature—Miscellaneous (Box 131, Folder 13)
  - Turtles—Literature—Trade (Box 131, Folder 14)
  - Turtles—Miscellaneous (Box 131, Folder 15)
  - Turtles—Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 131, Folder 16)
  - Turtles—Project Plan (Animals in the Classroom—correspondence to find a physiologist who would do the survey to replace animals in experimentation with other methods). (Box 131, Folder 17)
  - Turtles—State Extraction Laws (Box 131, Folder 18)
  - Turtles—Survey Requests (Box 131, Folder 19)
  - Turtles—Survey, Cover Letter and Results (Box 131, Folder 20)
  - Turtles—Zoe’s Notes (Zoe Rappoport, Researcher, PETA, Research, Investigations and Rescue Department; 1995) (Box 131, Folder 21)
  - Types of Alternatives—Agarose Diffusion Test (Box 131, Folder 22)
  - Types of Alternatives—Ames Test (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - Types of Alternatives—Cadavers (Box 132, Folder 2)
  - Types of Alternatives—Cell and Tissue Cultures - 1 of 6 (Box 132, Folder 3)
  - Types of Alternatives—Cell and Tissue Cultures - 2 of 6 (Box 132, Folder 4)
  - Types of Alternatives—Cell and Tissue Cultures - 3 of 6 (Box 132, Folder 5)
  - Types of Alternatives—Cell and Tissue Cultures - 4 of 6 (Box 132, Folder 6)
  - Types of Alternatives—Cell and Tissue Cultures - 5 of 6 (Box 132, Folder 7)
  - Types of Alternatives—Cell and Tissue Cultures - 6 of 6 (Box 132, Folder 8)
  - Types of Alternatives—Clinical Studies (Box 132, Folder 9)
  - Types of Alternatives—Computers (The Alternatives Report: Covering replacement, reduction and refinement in animal research and testing, Vol. 1., no. 1; May/June 1989) - 1 of 4 (Box 132, Folder 10)
  - Types of Alternatives—Computers (The Alternatives Report: Covering replacement, reduction and refinement in animal research and testing, Vol. 1., no. 1; May/June 1989) - 2 of 4 (Box 132, Folder 11)
  - Types of Alternatives—Computers (The Alternatives Report: Covering replacement, reduction and refinement in animal research and testing, Vol. 1., no. 1; May/June 1989) - 3 of 4 (Box 132, Folder 12)
  - Types of Alternatives—Computers (The Alternatives Report: Covering replacement, reduction and refinement in animal research and testing, Vol. 1., no. 1; May/June 1989) - 4 of 4 (Box 132, Folder 10)
  - Types of Alternatives—Eggs (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - Types of Alternatives—Gas Chromatography (Box 133, Folder 2)
  - Types of Alternatives—Gelatin (Box 133, Folder 3)
  - Urinary/Digestive (vivisection) (Box 133, Folder 4)
  - Wildlife Experiments 2” (Pesticides, agricultural runoff, raising alligators for skins, vaccines used in animals in the wild may spread immunity for rabies, deliberately crippling wild ducks to see how they fend for themselves with impediments, etc.) - 1 of 2 (Box 133, Folder 5)
  - Wildlife Experiments 2” (Pesticides, agricultural runoff, raising alligators for skins, vaccines used in animals in the wild may spread immunity for rabies, deliberately crippling wild ducks to see how they fend for themselves with impediments, etc.) - 2 of 2 (Box 133, Folder 6)
  - Worms (Box 133, Folder 7)
  - Wounds (Box 133, Folder 8)
  - Xenograft Information Packs (Box 133, Folder 9)
  - Xenografts—Baboon Liver—1st Case (35 y/o) (Box 133, Folder 10)
  - Xenografts—Baboon Liver—2nd Case (62 y/o) (Box 133, Folder 11)
  - Xenografts—Baboon Marrow - 1 of 2 (Box 133, Folder 12)
  - Xenografts—Baboon Marrow - 2 of 2 (Box 133, Folder 13)
  - Xenografts—Baby Fae Heart - 1 of 7 (Box 134, Folder 1)
  - Xenografts—Baby Fae Heart - 2 of 7 (Box 134, Folder 2)
  - Xenografts—Baby Fae Heart - 3 of 7 (Box 134, Folder 3)
  - Xenografts—Baby Fae Heart - 4 of 7 (Box 134, Folder 4)
  - Xenografts—Baby Fae Heart - 5 of 7 (Box 134, Folder 5)
  - Xenografts—Baby Fae Heart - 6 of 7 (Box 134, Folder 6)
  - Xenografts—Baby Fae Heart - 7 of 7 (Box 134, Folder 7)
  - Xenografts—General - 1 of 9 (the use of nonhuman animals as organ donors—transgression of species boundaries, particularly those between humans and other animals. “Animal advocacy (rights) prioritizes the individual and his or her well-being. By contrast much of environmental politics tends to focus on communities or populations....” from Lynda Birke and Mike Michael, “The Heart of the Matter: Animal Bodies, Ethics, and Species Boundaries,” Society and Animals¸6.3, 245ff.) 4” (Box 134, Folder 8)
  - Xenografts—General - 2 of 9 (Box 134, Folder 9)
  - Xenografts—General - 3 of 9 (Box 134, Folder 10)
  - Xenografts—General - 4 of 9 (Box 134, Folder 11)
  - Xenografts—General - 5 of 9 (Box 134, Folder 12)
  - Xenografts - 6 of 9 (Box 135, Folder 1)
  - Xenografts - 7 of 9 (Box 135, Folder 2)
  - Xenografts - 8 of 9 (Box 135, Folder 3)
  - Xenografts - 9 of 9 (Box 135, Folder 4)
  - Xenographs—Pig’s liver (Box 135, Folder 5)
  - Zoononotic Illnesses—Wildlife (Box 135, Folder 6)
- Subject Files, 8 linear feet
  - Accidents (Box 135, Folder 7)
  - Animal Care Committees - 1 of 2 (Box 135, Folder 8)
  - Animal Care Committees - 2 of 2 (Box 135, Folder 9)
  - Bad Organizations (50 clippings, photocopies paperclipped to the originals) - 1 of 2 (Box 136, Folder 1)
  - Bad Organizations (50 clippings, photocopies paperclipped to the originals) - 2 of 2 (Box 136, Folder 2)
  - Cancer—Failure of Research- 1 of 4 (Box 136, Folder 3)
  - Cancer—Failure of Research- 2 of 4 (Box 136, Folder 4)
  - Cancer—Failure of Research- 3 of 4 (Box 136, Folder 5)
  - Cancer—Failure of Research- 4 of 4 (Box 136, Folder 6)
  - Capture (Box 136, Folder 7)
  - Collisions—Airplanes (Box 136, Folder 8)
  - Collisions—General/Miscellaneous—Wildlife—Condors (Box 136, Folder 9)
  - Collisions—Windmills (Box 136, Folder 10)
  - Collisions—Windows (Box 136, Folder 11)
  - Coral Reefs (Box 136, Folder 12)
  - Cystic fibrosis—animals used in searching for identification of cause and treatment. (Box 136, Folder 13)
  - Dental and list of individual schools and membership lists; and the use of Oral-B tooth brushes made by a company like Gillette was dedicating millions to influence legislators, the media and the general public that the use of animal testing is necessary to produce safe consumer products - 1 of 2 (Box 136, Folder 14)
  - Dental - 2 of 2 (Box 136, Folder 15)
  - Diabetes. Use of rodents and dogs “The Truth behind the discovery of Insulin” by Brandon Reines (The American Anti-Vivisection Society, (1995?) (Box 137, Folder 1)
  - Down’s Syndrome. Small file. (Box 137, Folder 2)
  - Driftnets—Dolphins - 1 of 6 (Box 137, Folder 3)
  - Driftnets—Dolphins - 2 of 6 (Box 137, Folder 4)
  - Driftnets—Dolphins - 3 of 6 (Box 137, Folder 5)
  - Driftnets—Dolphins - 4 of 6 (Box 137, Folder 6)
  - Driftnets—Dolphins - 5 of 6 (Box 137, Folder 7)
  - Driftnets—Dolphins - 6 of 6 (Box 137, Folder 8)
  - Driftnets—General/Miscellaneous - 1 of 4 (Box 137, Folder 9)
  - Driftnets—General/Miscellaneous - 2 of 4 (Box 137, Folder 10)
  - Driftnets—General/Miscellaneous - 3 of 4 (Box 137, Folder 11)
  - Driftnets—General/Miscellaneous - 4 of 4 (Box 137, Folder 12)
  - Driftnets—Turtles - 1 of 2 (Box 137, Folder 13)
  - Driftnets—Turtles - 2 of 2 (Box 137, Folder 14)
  - Drowning/Decompression. Use especially of dogs in experimentation; studies of the numbers of dogs used, the conditions to which they are subjected (Undersea Biomedical Research, Vol. 12, No. 3, September 1985: “Pressure in the treatment of spinal cord decompression sickness.”; Journal of Applied Physiology, Vol. 57, 1984: “...lungs of dogs to acute decompression.”) Dogs also drowned for research. (Box 138, Folder 1)
  - Drug Testing—General - 1 of 2 (Box 138, Folder 2)
  - Drug Testing—General - 2 of 2 (Box 138, Folder 3)
  - Drug Testing—Types of Animals—Dogs Today: Newspaper of the Year, November 20, 1989, an expose of the Huntingdon Research Centre in Cambridge. (Box 138, Folder 4)
  - Drug Testing—Types of Animals—Pigs (Box 138, Folder 5)
  - Drug Testing—Types of Animals—Primates (Box 138, Folder 6)
  - Drug Testing—Types of Animals—Rabbits (Box 138, Folder 7)
  - Drug Testing—Types of Animals—Rodents—General/Miscellaneous (Box 138, Folder 8)
  - Drug Testing—Types of Animals—Rodents, Mice (Box 138, Folder 9)
  - Drug Testing—Types of Animals—Rodents, Rats (Box 138, Folder 10)
  - Drug Testing—Types of Animals—Unspecified (Box 138, Folder 11)
  - Drug-Testing—Types of Animals—Miscellaneous. Aspertane, Dopomen, Ventolin Inhaler; Tylenol; “Toxic pollutants and how they affect aquatic and terrestrial environmentals—use of animal experimentation (Box 138, Folder 12)
  - Epilepsy (Box 139, Folder 1)
  - Equipment (Box 139, Folder 2)
  - Exercise (Box 139, Folder 3)
  - “Experimenting on Cetaceans: Some ethical considerations...” Dale Jamieson, Asst. Prof, Dept. of Philosophy; SUNY, College at Fredonia, Fredonia, NY. April 28-May 2 1980. - missing folder (Box 139, Folder 4)
  - Eyes/Vision—100 pp. print out listing grants and programs using animal subjects (1985). 3” (Box 139, Folder 5)
  - Feeding Wildlife (Box 139, Folder 6)
  - Fetal Tissue (Box 139, Folder 7)
  - Flea Control (Box 139, Folder 8)
  - Food (Box 139, Folder 9)
  - General/Miscellaneous—Laboratory Animal Welfare (treatment, whistleblowers, legislation, etc.) - 1 of 9 (Box 140, Folder 1)
  - General/Miscellaneous—Laboratory Animal Welfare (treatment, whistleblowers, legislation, etc.) - 2 of 9 (Box 140, Folder 2)
  - General/Miscellaneous—Laboratory Animal Welfare (treatment, whistleblowers, legislation, etc.) - 3 of 9 (Box 140, Folder 3)
  - General/Miscellaneous—Laboratory Animal Welfare (treatment, whistleblowers, legislation, etc.) - 4 of 9 (Box 140, Folder 4)
  - General/Miscellaneous—Laboratory Animal Welfare (treatment, whistleblowers, legislation, etc.) - 5 of 9 (Box 140, Folder 5)
  - General/Miscellaneous—Laboratory Animal Welfare (treatment, whistleblowers, legislation, etc.) - 6 of 9 (Box 140, Folder 6)
  - General/Miscellaneous—Laboratory Animal Welfare (treatment, whistleblowers, legislation, etc.) - 7 of 9 (Box 140, Folder 7)
  - General/Miscellaneous—Laboratory Animal Welfare (treatment, whistleblowers, legislation, etc.) - 8 of 9 (Box 140, Folder 8)
  - General/Miscellaneous—Laboratory Animal Welfare (treatment, whistleblowers, legislation, etc.) - 9 of 9 (Box 140, Folder 9)
  - Genetic engineering—Agriculture. 3’’ Searching for the perfect pig, cows that give more milk; gene-altered food; Dolly the cloned sheep; green mouse glows in the dark (1987); “Patenting: The Newest Form of Animal Exploitation” (Fall, 1987; No.2)—Animal Legal Defense Fund Newsletter. Manipulation. (Box 141, Folder 1)
  - Hog-human health projects.. Box about 2/3 full. 3” (Box 141, Folder 2)
  - Homosexuality—Abstracts (US) (Box 141, Folder 3)
  - Homosexuality—Abstracts—Foreign Countries (Box 141, Folder 4)
  - Homosexuality—Goth, Sweden (Box 141, Folder 5)
  - Homosexuality—Homosexuality Research (Box 141, Folder 6)
  - Homosexuality—Miscellaneous (Box 142, Folder 1)
  - Homosexuality—Research Institutions (Box 142, Folder 2)
  - Homosexuality—U.S. Government Grants (Box 142, Folder 3)
  - Horses (United Action for Animals, Inc.; wild horses; trotters. (Box 142, Folder 4)
  - Housing - 1 of 3 (Box 142, Folder 5)
  - Housing - 2 of 3 (Box 142, Folder 6)
  - Housing - 3 of 3 (Box 142, Folder 7)
  - Immunology—experimentation - 1 of 2 (Box 142, Folder 8)
  - Immunology—experimentation - 2 of 2 (Box 142, Folder 9)
  - Impact—experimentation (Box 142, Folder 10)
  - Inspection (Box 142, Folder 11)
  - Intelligence/Learning—experimentation (Box 142, Folder 12)
  - Language—experimentation - 1 of 3 (Box 142, Folder 13)
  - Language—experimentation - 2 of 3 (Box 142, Folder 14)
  - Language—experimentation - 3 of 3 (Box 142, Folder 15)
  - Laser Research—experimentation (Box 142, Folder 16)
  - Leprosy—experimentation - 1 of 2 (Box 143, Folder 1)
  - Leprosy—experimentation - 2 of 2 (Box 143, Folder 2)
  - Leukemia—experimentation (Box 143, Folder 3)
  - Live Import/Export - 1 of 6 (Box 143, Folder 4)
  - Live Import/Export - 2 of 6 (Box 143, Folder 5)
  - Live Import/Export - 3 of 6 (Box 143, Folder 6)
  - Live Import/Export - 4 of 6 (Box 143, Folder 7)
  - Live Import/Export - 5 of 6 (Box 143, Folder 8)
  - Live Import/Export - 6 of 6 (Box 143, Folder 9)
  - Locomotion—experimentation (Box 143, Folder 10)
  - Lou Gehrigs Disease—experimentation (Box 143, Folder 11)
  - Lung/Respiratory—experimentation (Box 143, Folder 12)
  - Lyme Disease—experimentation (Box 143, Folder 13)
  - Malaria—experimentation (Box 143, Folder 14)
  - Marine Mammals (Testing of sonar on dolphins, sharks, whales, manatees, seals, etc. (Box 143, Folder 7)
  - Memory—experimentation (Box 143, Folder 15)
  - Military—Biological/Chemical Warfare (Box 143, Folder 16)
  - Military—General/Miscellaneous—experimentation, vivisection - 1 of 4 (Box 144, Folder 1)
  - Military—General/Miscellaneous—experimentation, vivisection - 2 of 4 (Box 144, Folder 2)
  - Military—General/Miscellaneous—experimentation, vivisection - 3 of 4 (Box 144, Folder 3)
  - Military—General/Miscellaneous—experimentation, vivisection - 4 of 4 (Box 144, Folder 4)
  - Military—Marine (Box 144, Folder 5)
  - Military—Radiation (Box 144, Folder 6)
  - Military—Space (Box 144, Folder 7)
  - Military—wound (Box 144, Folder 8)
  - Mink (Mink Farming—how to; Mink Research projects—‘81-’91 Print-out from the NIH requested by Virginia Bollinger, requested on June 13, 1991. (Box 144, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 144, Folder 10)
  - Monthly Reports 1996—Research, Investigations and Rescue (RIR) (Box 144, Folder 11)
  - Monthly Reports 1997—Research, Investigations and Rescue (RIR) (Box 144, Folder 12)
  - Oil Spills - 1 of 4 (Box 145, Folder 1)
  - Oil Spills - 2 of 4 (Box 145, Folder 2)
  - Oil Spills - 3 of 4 (Box 145, Folder 3)
  - Oil Spills - 4 of 4 (Box 145, Folder 4)
  - Other Groups (125 clippings, photocopies paperclipped to the originals) - 1 of 4 (Box 145, Folder 5)
  - Other Groups (125 clippings, photocopies paperclipped to the originals) - 2 of 4 (Box 145, Folder 6)
  - Other Groups (125 clippings, photocopies paperclipped to the originals) - 3 of 4 (Box 145, Folder 7)
  - Other Groups (125 clippings, photocopies paperclipped to the originals) - 4 of 4 (Box 145, Folder 8)
  - Overpopulation - 1 of 4 (Box 145, Folder 9)
  - Overpopulation - 2 of 4 (Box 145, Folder 10)
  - Overpopulation - 3 of 4 (Box 145, Folder 11)
  - Overpopulation - 4 of 4 (Box 145, Folder 12)
  - Pain 3” - 1 of 4 (Box 145.1, Folder 1)
  - Pain 3” - 2 of 4 (Box 145.1, Folder 2)
  - Pain 3” - 3 of 4 (Box 145.1, Folder 3)
  - Pain 3” - 4 of 4 (Box 145.1, Folder 4)
  - “Pest” Control—Contraception—General/Miscellaneous - 1 of 4 (Box 146, Folder 1)
  - “Pest” Control—Contraception—General/Miscellaneous - 2 of 4 (Box 146, Folder 2)
  - “Pest” Control—Contraception—General/Miscellaneous - 3 of 4 (Box 146, Folder 3)
  - “Pest” Control—Contraception—General/Miscellaneous - 4 of 4 (Box 146, Folder 4)
  - “Pest” Control—General/Miscellaneous - 1 of 5 (Box 146, Folder 5)
  - “Pest” Control—General/Miscellaneous - 2 of 5 (Box 146, Folder 6)
  - “Pest” Control—General/Miscellaneous - 3 of 5 (Box 146, Folder 7)
  - “Pest” Control—General/Miscellaneous - 4 of 5 (Box 146, Folder 8)
  - “Pest” Control—General/Miscellaneous - 5 of 5 (Box 146, Folder 9)
  - “Pest” Control—Humane Traps - 1 of 2 (Box 146, Folder 10)
  - “Pest” Control—Humane Traps - 2 of 2 (Box 146, Folder 11)
  - Psychological Well-Being - 1 of 3 (Box 146, Folder 12)
  - Psychological Well-Being - 2 of 3 (Box 146, Folder 13)
  - Psychological Well-Being - 3 of 3 (Box 146, Folder 14)
  - Psychology—Maternal Deprivation/Child Abuse--experimentation - 1 of 3 (Box 146.1, Folder 1)
  - Psychology—Maternal Deprivation/Child Abuse--experimentation - 2 of 3 (Box 146.1, Folder 2)
  - Psychology—Maternal Deprivation/Child Abuse--experimentation - 3 of 3 (Box 146.1, Folder 3)
  - Restraint (Box 147, Folder 1)
  - Retirement Plans - 1 0f 2 (Box 147, Folder 2)
  - Retirement Plans - 2 of 2 (Box 147, Folder 3)
  - Sanitation (Box 147, Folder 4)
  - Smuggling (Live)/Poaching—general. 4”. - 1 of 8 (Box 147, Folder 5)
  - Smuggling (Live)/Poaching—general. 4”. - 2 of 8 (Box 147, Folder 6)
  - Smuggling (Live)/Poaching—general. 4”. - 3 of 8 (Box 147, Folder 7)
  - Smuggling (Live)/Poaching—general. 4”. - 4 of 8 (Box 147, Folder 8)
  - Smuggling (Live)/Poaching—general. 4”. - 5 of 8 (Box 147, Folder 9)
  - Smuggling (Live)/Poaching—general. 4”. - 6 of 8 (Box 147, Folder 10)
  - Smuggling (Live)/Poaching—general. 4”. - 7 of 8 (Box 147, Folder 11)
  - Smuggling (Live)/Poaching—general. 4”. - 8 of 8 (Box 147, Folder 12)
  - Transportation (Box 147, Folder 13)
  - Vivisection (3) (75 clippings, photocopies paperclipped to the originals) - 1 of 3 (Box 148, Folder 1)
  - Vivisection (3) (75 clippings, photocopies paperclipped to the originals) - 2 of 3 (Box 148, Folder 2)
  - Vivisection (3) (75 clippings, photocopies paperclipped to the originals) - 3 of 3 (Box 148, Folder 3)
  - Vivisection (4) (200 clippings, photocopies paperclipped to the originals) - 1 of 3 (Box 148, Folder 4)
  - Vivisection (4) (200 clippings, photocopies paperclipped to the originals) - 2 of 3 (Box 148, Folder 5)
  - Vivisection (4) (200 clippings, photocopies paperclipped to the originals) - 3 of 3 (Box 148, Folder 6)
  - Vivisection (5) (300 clippings, photocopies paperclipped to the originals) - 1 of 6 (Box 149, Folder 1)
  - Vivisection (5) (300 clippings, photocopies paperclipped to the originals) - 2 of 6 (Box 149, Folder 2)
  - Vivisection (5) (300 clippings, photocopies paperclipped to the originals) - 3 of 6 (Box 149, Folder 3)
  - Vivisection (5) (300 clippings, photocopies paperclipped to the originals) - 4 of 6 (Box 149, Folder 4)
  - Vivisection (5) (300 clippings, photocopies paperclipped to the originals) - 5 of 6 (Box 149, Folder 5)
  - Vivisection (5) (300 clippings, photocopies paperclipped to the originals) - 6 of 6 (Box 149, Folder 6)
  - Wildlife (1) (150 clippings, photocopies paperclipped to the originals) - 1 of 3 (Box 150, Folder 1)
  - Wildlife (1) (150 clippings, photocopies paperclipped to the originals) - 2 of 3 (Box 150, Folder 2)
  - Wildlife (1) (150 clippings, photocopies paperclipped to the originals) - 3 of 3 (Box 150, Folder 3)
  - Wildlife (2)”Two large expandable folders “To Be Coded—Wildlife (2)” - 1 of 5 (Box 150, Folder 4)
  - Wildlife (2)”Two large expandable folders “To Be Coded—Wildlife (2)” - 2 of 5 (Box 150, Folder 5)
  - Wildlife (2)”Two large expandable folders “To Be Coded—Wildlife (2)” - 3 of 5 (Box 150, Folder 6)
  - Wildlife (2)”Two large expandable folders “To Be Coded—Wildlife (2)” - 4 of 5 (Box 150.1, Folder 1)
  - Wildlife (2)”Two large expandable folders “To Be Coded—Wildlife (2)” - 5 of 5 (Box 150.1, Folder 2)
  - Wildlife(3)” From 1988-2000. Total clippings 600 items, with photocopies of clippings from newspapers and journals; subjects cover everything from the problem of cats and the survival of the plover along the NC coast to animals used in testing; turtles, sonar testing and whales, West Nile virus and the avian population, etc. - 1 of 6 (Box 151, Folder 1)
  - Wildlife(3)” From 1988-2000. Total clippings 600 items, with photocopies of clippings from newspapers and journals; subjects cover everything from the problem of cats and the survival of the plover along the NC coast to animals used in testing; turtles, sonar testing and whales, West Nile virus and the avian population, etc. - 2 of 6 (Box 151, Folder 2)
  - Wildlife(3)” From 1988-2000. Total clippings 600 items, with photocopies of clippings from newspapers and journals; subjects cover everything from the problem of cats and the survival of the plover along the NC coast to animals used in testing; turtles, sonar testing and whales, West Nile virus and the avian population, etc. - 3 of 6 (Box 151, Folder 3)
  - Wildlife(3)” From 1988-2000. Total clippings 600 items, with photocopies of clippings from newspapers and journals; subjects cover everything from the problem of cats and the survival of the plover along the NC coast to animals used in testing; turtles, sonar testing and whales, West Nile virus and the avian population, etc. - 4 of 6 (Box 151, Folder 4)
  - Wildlife(3)” From 1988-2000. Total clippings 600 items, with photocopies of clippings from newspapers and journals; subjects cover everything from the problem of cats and the survival of the plover along the NC coast to animals used in testing; turtles, sonar testing and whales, West Nile virus and the avian population, etc. - 5 of 6 (Box 151, Folder 5)
  - Wildlife(3)” From 1988-2000. Total clippings 600 items, with photocopies of clippings from newspapers and journals; subjects cover everything from the problem of cats and the survival of the plover along the NC coast to animals used in testing; turtles, sonar testing and whales, West Nile virus and the avian population, etc. - 6 of 6 (Box 151, Folder 6)
- Other Files, 1.5 linear feet
  - Types of Alternatives - Epidemiological Studies (Original Box 3, 2 Folders)) - 1 of 2 (Box 152, Folder 1)
  - Types of Alternatives - Epidemiological Studies (Original Box 3, 2 Folders)) - 2 of 2 (Box 152, Folder 2)
  - In Vitro International (RoPak Laboratories) (Original Box 3, 2 Folders)) - 1 of 2 (Box 152, Folder 3)
  - In Vitro International (RoPak Laboratories) (Original Box 3, 2 Folders)) - 1 of 2 (Box 152, Folder 4)
  - Transplants - General - Positive (Original Box 5, 4 Folders) - 1 of 4 (Box 152, Folder 5)
  - Transplants - General - Positive (Original Box 5, 4 Folders) - 2 of 4 (Box 152, Folder 6)
  - Transplants - General - Positive (Original Box 5, 4 Folders) - 3 of 4 (Box 152, Folder 7)
  - Transplants - General - Positive (Original Box 5, 4 Folders) - 4 of 4 (Box 152, Folder 8)
  - Captive Animals Protective Society Animal Reports, 1992-1996(Original Box 2, 1 Folder) (Box 152, Folder 9)
  - Animal Rights America(Original Box 10, 1 Folder) (Box 152, Folder 10)
  - American Farmland Trust(Original Box 13, 1 Folder) (Box 152, Folder 11)
  - American Fun Resources Institute(Original Box 13, 1 Folder) (Box 152, Folder 12)
  - Fun Industry Mobilization Fund (Original Box 13, 1 Folder) (Box 152, Folder 13)
  - Australian Meat and Livestock(Original Box 13, 1 Folder) (Box 152, Folder 14)
  - Future Farmers of America (Original Box 13, 1 Folder) (Box 152, Folder 15)
  - National Marine Fisheries Service - Anti-Animal Org.(Original Box 15, 1 Folder) (Box 152, Folder 16)
  - Maryland Saltwater Sportsfisherman's Assoc.(Original Box 15, 1 Folder) (Box 152, Folder 17)
  - Experimentation - Propaganda, 1986(Original Box 20, 1 Folder) (Box 152, Folder 18)
  - Experimentation - Propaganda, 1987(Original Box 20, 1 Folder) (Box 152, Folder 19)
  - Sweden(Original Box 21, 1 Folder) (Box 153, Folder 1)
  - Vaccines(Original Box 25, 1 Folder) (Box 153, Folder 2)
  - Xenografts - Baboon Liver - Gen./Misc.(Original Box 25, 1 Folder) (Box 153, Folder 3)
  - American Humane Education Society (MA)(Original Box 27, 1 Folder) (Box 153, Folder 4)
  - Boston Marine Mammal Coalition(Original Box 27, 1 Folder) (Box 153, Folder 5)
  - Mountain Lion Presentation Foundation(Original Box 30, 2 Folders) - 1 of 2 (Box 153, Folder 6)
  - Mountain Lion Presentation Foundation(Original Box 30, 2 Folders) - 2 of 2 (Box 153, Folder 7)
  - Performing Animal Welfare Society (PAWS)(Original Box 30, 1 Folder) (Box 153, Folder 8)